meippai senobi shitekita kedo
Even though I’ve been stretching myself as far as I can
kimi no mae ja umaku dekinai
I just can’t do it well when I’m in front of you
tansan ga nukeru yori hayai supiido de
My feelings are changing faster
kawatte iku kimochi
Than soda losing its fizz
mada jibun demo~ kizuitenai
I haven’t even noticed it myself yet
nee
saisho ni nozonda mirai~ to wa~ sukoshi chigau keredo
Hey
It’s a little different from the future I wished for in the beginning, but
saigo wa nanimo iranai~ tada~ soba ni ite~
In the end, I don’t need anything—just stay by my side
bukiyou de surechigatte kangurutte bakka boku tachi wa
Clumsy and always missing each other, overthinking everything—that’s just how we are
ienai ienai nante katte nan darou~
Saying “I can’t say it” over and over—how selfish is that?
kimi ga iru asu ga ii na tte omotteitatte kaerarenai
Even if I think I want a tomorrow where you’re there, I can’t change it
tsutaenakucha~
I have to tell you